(Penny:)Oh, hey, Sheldon.
What you got there? New comic book?
(Sheldon:)Old comic book.
(Sheldon:)I just retrieved it
from my safe-deposit box.
(Penny:)What do you have
a safe-deposit box for?
(Sheldon:)Old comic books.
(Sheldon:)I lost this to Wolowitz
in an ill-considered cricket wager.
(Penny:)What, do they have Wii cricket now?
(Penny:)That can't be very popular.
(Sheldon:)Penny, I'd rather not talk about it.
(Penny:)Well, if it makes you feel any better,
I'm not feeling so hot either.
(Sheldon:)Why would that make me feel better?
(Penny:)I don't know, empathy?
(Penny:)I'm just saying that you're feeling upset
about something with Howard...
(Penny:)...and I'm upset about something
with Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Yes, the disappointing sex.
(Sheldon:)That's an inexact parallel.
(Sheldon:)You and Leonard can always return
to being friends.
(Sheldon:)I can never return to a state
in which Wolowitz has not bested me...
(Sheldon:)...like Mrs. Riley's chicken.